I'm not gay, by the way. I feel like I
need to
address that up top.
A lot of people assume that I'm gay
because I look
gay.
>> There's still time.
>> But
I got some gays in the crowd.
Nice. Thanks for Did you know that I
wasn't gay?
>> Yeah.
>> You did?
They're trying to get me.
>> [laughter]
>> They are.
I swear. I don't know if numbers are
down, but they're like heavily
recruiting.
>> [laughter]
>> They're a lot like ISIS.
Yeah, I know.
No requirements at all. Just
>> [cheering]
>> Just join us. Here's some Carhartt. Get
out there.
Yeah. Oh, it's Sorry. We shouldn't joke
about it.
>> [laughter]
>> It's tough. My brother's wife was
actually recently taken by a lesbian.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> She wanted to be taken, but still
>> [laughter]
>> ISIS and lesbians out there
ripping families apart.
Call your congress people about it.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know why I look like this.
I hang out with a lot of lesbians. Like
I've got a lot of lesbian friends, so I
think maybe they're just sort of rubbing
off on me. Not like that, but you know.
>> [music]
[music]
[laughter]
>> It's good to be here. Thank you so much
for COMING OUT. UM
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> I LOVE SAN DIEGO. ONE OF MY FAVORITE
PLACES in the world.
Just me. All right.
I love it.
Actually, I lost my virginity in San
Diego.
>> [cheering]
>> YEAH.
>> [laughter]
>> I DIDN'T EVEN LIKE THE GUY. That's just
how much I loved San Diego.
>> [cheering and applause]
[laughter]
>> But great place to lose your virginity
if you're thinking about it, sir. San
Diego.
Yeah.
Consider it.
>> [laughter]
>> Just cuz even if it doesn't go very
well, you're still in an awesome place,
right?
Mine went okay. Thanks for asking. Um
No, it was bad.
But then I had the rest of the day in
San Diego, so
went to the beach,
got a burrito,
then I got ready for the show and came
here. It was A GOOD DAY.
>> [applause]
>> I WAS A LATE BLOOMER. I WAS THE LAST OF
my friend group to go through puberty.
And uh I remember this my best friend
Jessica at the time she went through
puberty first and she got like all the
curves in all the right places and I
didn't. We looked like Kermit and Miss
Piggy right next to each other.
Um
but one day she was like, "Me and some
girls are going to go shopping for bras.
We need new bras." And I didn't, but I
didn't want to be left out, so I was
like, "Yeah.
Me, too.
Let's go."
So we went shopping and it's weird
shopping for something that you can't
fill yet.
It's sort of like if the Padres went
shopping for a trophy case. It's like,
"You know, let's wait
a little bit."
They'll start coming in soon, maybe, you
know, but just like save your money for
now and
>> [laughter]
>> it's fine.
No, but we went
we went shopping. I thought we were
going to go to Walmart and get training
bras, but we went to the mall and we
went to Victoria's Secret.
And they don't have training bras there.
They have game day professional
major league bras.
And I wasn't ready for the majors. I was
like, "Where's your minor league
section? Where's your Padres section? I
need the
>> [laughter]
>> Where's your tatties junior bras? I
mean, so
My tatties are small, so I need the
junior brands.
I ended up getting a bra to grow into.
>> [laughter]
>> So, any day now.
Boobs are weird.
>> [laughter]
>> Right? Cuz you really want them before
you have them cuz all your friends have
them.
And then you get them and they're fun
for a little bit, but then they get old.
>> [laughter]
>> It kind of grows.
And a lot of people are just getting rid
of them.
Boobs are a lot like air fryers.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Like they're really great if you need to
feed kids quickly.
But other than that, they're just kind
of a waste of space.
>> [laughter]
>> They're hard to run with.
Anybody have kids?
Yeah,
nice. [applause]
Oh, yeah, you two have kids?
You have one? Nice. How are their
boobs coming in? Are they
He?
He's have boobs, too.
How old is he?
22? Give it, yeah, 7, 8 years.
>> [laughter]
>> I have a bra he can have if he wants
[laughter] it.
Is um
is anybody celebrating anything? No,
okay, cool. I am
I have a birthday this year.
Um
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you.
Yeah.
Appreciate it.
I don't usually do stuff on my
birthdays. Like I don't really
celebrate. The most I'll do is I'll like
go out to dinner with my family.
Um but I've noticed that people in my
life they keep suggesting things that I
should do for this birthday coming up.
But I think it's just things that they
want to do
on my birthday.
Like my sister-in-law was like, "You
know what you should do for your
birthday?
Girls' trip."
>> [laughter]
>> Girls' trip, no kids.
[laughter]
>> But I don't have kids. Why would I care
if there's kids? You can bring your I
like your kids. I don't
My boyfriend, he was like, "You know
what you could do for your birthday? I
hear a lot of people are doing this.
Could be a good time. You could
take one of those pole dancing classes."
>> [laughter]
>> Invite some of your friends. Invite that
one friend Jess.
the
>> [laughter]
>> I'll go to the recital.
[laughter]
>> Bring my camcorder.
It'll be good.
>> [laughter]
>> I've had to tell my dad to stop getting
me gifts for my birthday because one
year he asked me what I wanted and I
told him that I wanted a Theragun
and he didn't know what that was. He
assumed it was a real gun.
>> [laughter]
>> Like word got back to me that he was
going to gun shops
looking for a gun for me.
And I called him up and I clarified. I
was like, "No, it's not a gun. It's a
massager for your muscles, like a
massage gun."
And he was like, "Oh, okay."
And then I forgot about this and my
birthday comes around and he hands me a
gift and I open it and it's a
Hitachi Magic Wand.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> I was like, "Dad, why did you
WHY DID YOU GET ME THIS?"
>> [laughter]
>> He's like, "Oh, you said you wanted a
massager."
And to his credit, that's what it says
on the box.
Hitachi's very coy with its branding.
Like there's even a photo on the box of
an old lady using it on her neck.
>> [laughter]
>> That's false advertising.
That would kill her. That's not okay.
It's a very powerful machine.
>> [laughter]
>> But he was like, "Oh, did I get you the
wrong thing? Do you want me to return
it?" I was like, "No, no, no, no, no."
>> [applause]
>> I'll find a use for it.
I guess.
He's like, "All right. Well,
pass it around. Let everybody take a
look at it.
>> [laughter]
>> Spent good money on that thing."
So I did. I slid the box to my grandpa,
who was right next to me.
He fully took it out of the box, started
playing with all the settings, trying
them out on his quads right here.
Now, I can't get that image out of my
head.
Every time I use it, that's what I'm
thinking about.
>> [laughter]
>> And I still get off. That's how good of
a product it is.
It's pretty
amazing.
>> [applause]
>> I highly recommend it for your
daughter's next
birthday.
But, I think the only other person at
the table who knew what it was, besides
me, was the Benihana chef.
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz he was just like,
[laughter]
[applause and cheering]
[applause]
>> "Weird white family." That's what he
said. I heard him say that.
I live in LA. I live in a very old
apartment building with very thin walls.
And the other day, I heard my neighbor
having sex. And I don't like hearing my
neighbor have sex. I love it.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I'm just kidding. I don't like it. I
don't like it. It's weird. It's loud.
It's distracting. Like, I'll just be at
my desk working. Like, I'll be in a Zoom
meeting, and then they'll start, and I
have to, you know, go on mute. I have to
turn my camera off, I have to go get my
magic wand and make sure
>> [applause]
>> I don't have time for that, you know, I
get busy.
>> [laughter]
>> But my neighbor, he's a single guy, so
he'll bring different women back over,
which is cool for me, I get some
variety.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm learning a lot.
Taking notes.
Learning Spanish.
>> [laughter]
>> I learned the word papi.
I don't know what it means, but one lady
kept saying it over and over again.
At first I thought she was ordering
bagels.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, that's too many bagels.
>> My neighbor, who I share wall with on
the other side of my apartment, she's an
actor, and so I can hear her doing her
self-tape auditions all the time, and
she knows I can hear her, and she's very
considerate. Like the other day she
texted me and she was like, "Hey, just
so you know, I have this audition I'm
going to do today, and it's for a horror
/ film,
>> [laughter]
>> and the scene is I'm getting chased
around a house by the killer.
So if you hear me screaming for help,
>> [laughter]
>> don't worry about it."
And then I was home when she started,
and she went for it. Like, she was good.
It sounded real. It was like so
convincing that I was like,
"Wait, maybe the killer texted me from
her phone.
Right before just to throw me off.
That'd be the perfect crime.
I like texted some of the other
neighbors. I was like, "Did she tell you
about the
audition?" They were like, "Yeah, yeah,
yeah, she told us."
I was like, "All right."
So, he texted everybody in the building.
>> [laughter]
>> Pretty good.
But, yeah, I tried to ignore it, but
then she was like we're getting more and
more into it. She started screaming for
help.
And so, I dropped what I was doing and
went and got my magic wand.
>> [applause]
>> I never checked on her. I hope she's
okay.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm sure she's fine.
>> I had a I had a good year. I made a
little extra money this year, so I
decided to Yeah, I decided to treat
myself a little bit. [applause]
And
I've never done this before for myself,
but I decided to get myself some health
insurance.
And
yeah, I went with Kaiser Permanente.
And uh yeah, I I signed up. I gave them
all my money and they were like, "All
right, you're good to go."
And um
>> [laughter]
>> a few days ago, I got a notification
from them that they dropped my coverage.
Just like randomly like that. And I was
pissed. I called them up. I was like,
"Hey, if you can just drop me like that,
like out of the blue,
maybe you shouldn't have the word
permanente in your name."
>> [applause]
>> I was like, "I'm still just learning
Spanish, but I think I know what that
word means."
Yeah, fool me.
But, he was like, "Oh, we had to drop
you because there was false information
on your application. The income that you
wrote down doesn't match what you made
last month."
And I was like, "Yeah, well, I'm an
artist.
My income is not
permanente."
It goes up and down, ente. I was like
trying to speak his language.
I was like, "Do you comprehende
what I'm saying?"
I was being a ente, to him.
But he was actually very nice and he
helped me get my plan back.
And so I was like, "All right. Thank
you, papi."
>> [applause]
>> I was
I was walking into a grocery store the
other day and there was a guy outside
with a clipboard and he was working for
autism awareness and I was like, "Oh,
I think YOU DID IT."
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> YEAH, I THINK EVERYBODY'S
>> [laughter]
>> AWARE NOW.
RIGHT? You guys know.
Like just then when I said autism
awareness, was anybody like, "What the
heck is she talking about?"
No, we all we're aware.
That's what I was telling the clipboard
guy.
I was like, "Great work, man.
>> [laughter]
>> You did it. You can go home, I think."
He was like, "Oh, you're taking the
words autism awareness very literally.
Do you know what that's a sign of?
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> He's good.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU SHOULD GET A RAISE.
>> I DO WONDER sometimes if I'm on the
spectrum,
but I haven't taken the official test,
but I did go online and I took the love
language quiz with my boyfriend.
>> [laughter]
>> And I feel like if you have to take that
quiz with your partner, you might be a
little bit
autistic.
>> [laughter]
>> Right? Like if you're like, "Oh,
you like to be touched?"
>> [laughter]
>> Commence touching.
>> And I need that. That helps me. I like
that.
Do you guys know the love language quiz?
Have you taken that one?
Yeah. Yeah, you've taken Do you know
your love language?
>> Yeah, quality time.
>> Quality time.
Nice. I was going to
move on to something else, but I'll just
spend some time with you
Now I feel bad if I was going to
>> [laughter]
>> What's your name?
Adam.
How are your parents doing?
>> They're not alive.
Oh,
They're not alive?
Do you want to talk about it?
Okay.
Nice. Is this your partner?
>> Yeah.
>> Do you know your love language?
>> Touch.
>> Touch? [laughter]
Hell yeah, dude.
>> [applause]
[laughter]
>> You want to like go with me?
>> [laughter]
>> Uh no, mine's not touch. That was really
hard for me, actually. I didn't like
that.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I like those um I like those
[clears throat] like dumb personality
quizzes that you can take online. I took
the Myers-Briggs quiz recently. Do you
know that one?
I got INTJ
and
>> [laughter]
>> that's not a very INTJ thing to do,
actually.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I got I got INTJ and if you're not
familiar with this one, the I stands for
introvert.
And you can only be two things. You can
be an introvert or you can be an
>> [applause and cheering]
>> I got the introvert one. That's just me.
But it's very true. I'm very
introverted. Like I've always had a
pretty tough time just participating in
group sex. Like I never really know
>> [laughter]
>> what to say or
I don't know how they want to be loved
yet. Like we haven't taken the quiz
together yet, so
it's tough.
But no, I um I prefer non-group sex, if
I'm being honest.
I prefer sex with one person,
and that person is myself.
>> [laughter]
>> Us INTJs, we love to accomplish a goal
in a timely and efficient manner.
And I figured out a way to do that.
>> [laughter]
>> Every time.
Um no, I like to I like to have sex with
my boyfriend, and I'm not just saying
that cuz he's here.
Great sex, babe.
And he's actually not here. Someone give
me a thumbs up back there. I don't know
who that was.
Sorry.
>> [laughter]
>> Some extrovert out there needing
attention or something.
No, any introverts here? Whisper at me.
Oh, wow. Yeah, a lot of lot of
introverts.
I have noticed that, like traveling
around doing these shows, a lot of
people who want to come see me do comedy
are a lot like me. Like a little bit
quiet and reserved and like super hot
and
like could be a model if they wanted to
be, but they're too busy like pursuing
the arts and
>> [laughter]
>> and very introverted. I get a lot of
introverted people out.
That's why like if you see anybody
tonight just like not laughing at all,
don't worry about it. That's just one of
my fans.
They're having a great time.
>> [laughter]
>> They're just thinking about how of a
time that they're having.
They're going to go home and journal
about how good of a time that they had
tonight.
So, it's fine.
Leave them alone.
>> [laughter]
>> But, I get it. I'm quiet. I don't talk
very much.
Sometimes my boyfriend thinks that I'm
giving him the silent treatment.
Like he'll be like, "Are you okay? Are
you mad at me?"
I'm like, "No, I'm fine." Why?
He's like, "Oh, you just
haven't spoken in 3 days, so."
Just checking in.
That's not my move. I don't do the
silent treatment. If I was mad at my
boyfriend, I would just
talk about him on stage.
But, yeah. My boyfriend does this really
annoying thing
>> [laughter]
>> where he likes to
communicate his feelings.
>> [laughter]
>> I know, right?
Yeah.
Like every time he has a feeling, he
wants to talk about it.
With me.
Every time I have a feeling,
like once a year,
I'll think about it
until I've figured it out in my head,
and then I'm like, "Oh, that wasn't even
worth feeling in the first place."
I'm so glad I didn't tell anybody about
that feeling.
That would have been embarrassing.
But, I'm getting better at listening to
his feelings and pretending they're
valid. It's good. We're growing.
I uh I people people get confused by my
demeanor, I think, just cuz like I don't
know, people think [clears throat] I'm
depressed just because I like don't
really talk or smile or have fun. And
um
like the other night after a show, I got
a DM from a stranger and it was just the
link to a suicide prevention hotline.
Yeah, I'm like, "Thanks, but don't worry
about it. I'm not depressed. I'm not
suicidal.
I would never kill myself.
But
what's the opposite of
killing yourself?
Like living life to the fullest? I would
never do that either. So, I don't know
where I'm at
>> [laughter]
>> on the spectrum
of life.
But
probably more on the kill myself side.
>> [laughter]
>> Just cuz like there's some signs.
Like
I don't wash lettuce anymore.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, like that's not worth it to me.
Like I would rather die than wash
and dry
lettuce. Like that's the worst part,
too, the drying. Cuz sometimes I'll
rinse it and then I'll try to dry it and
it just doesn't dry. [laughter]
So, then I'm just eating wet lettuce.
And I don't want to eat wet lettuce.
That's why I'm not gay.
>> [laughter]
>> It's a texture for me.
>> Anyways, I was taking the Myers-Briggs
quiz. I got INTJ.
And I actually didn't read that much
about my personality, but what I did was
I went to see the tab where they tell
you which famous people have your same
personality type, cuz that's the fun
part.
And the first person on the list for
mine was Jesus.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know how they got him to take
the quiz.
>> [laughter]
>> It's pretty good get.
>> No, it was probably just some guy
pretending to be Jesus, right? Like
taking the quiz at his computer.
After every question, he was like, "All
right.
What would Jesus do?"
Would Jesus have a messy workspace or
>> [laughter]
>> I think he got it wrong, though. I don't
think Jesus was an introvert.
No introvert has 12 friends. That's
crazy.
And Jesus turned water into wine to keep
the party going. That's not an introvert
thing.
I would do the opposite, turn
everybody's wine into water. We could go
home early.
Beat traffic.
Catch Jeopardy. that's yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Someone tried to clap for that.
These are my people.
Also, Jesus died on a cross. That's a
little dramatic for an introvert.
>> [laughter]
>> He picked the middle cross, too. Like up
on the hill in front of everybody. Like,
okay, diva.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know. Introvert, I would not be
caught dead middle cross. I would
I'd be side back cross.
I'd be humble about it.
That's just me, though.
>> [laughter]
>> The next person on the list, the famous
person list after Jesus, was Hitler.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
And I really don't know what Jesus and
Hitler
and me
>> [laughter]
>> all have in common.
Except that I've been thinking about it
and we're all
pretty gay-looking.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Right? Like, if you saw us all just like
walking down the street together,
but you didn't know us, you'd be like,
>> [laughter]
>> "Oh."
There must be some sort of a queer event
happening in the neighborhood.
>> [laughter]
>> Those gay autistic introverts are
brunch.
We're an interesting group.
Jesus, Hitler, and me.
Right?
Cuz you've got like the worst person in
the world and the best person in the
world, and then Jesus, right in the
middle of it.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> Oh, thank you. SO STUPID.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW. I DO FEEL A KINSHIP WITH
THEM NOW, THOUGH.
Like they're kind of like my spirit
guides at this point.
>> [laughter]
>> Like you know how people have a little
angel and a little devil on their
shoulders?
That's like me, but I got a little Jesus
and a little Hitler
on my shoulders,
guiding me through life,
telling me different things, you know,
pulling me in different directions.
Like little Hitler, he's always
>> [laughter]
>> he's always like reminding me that my
local library doesn't have a late
charge.
>> [laughter]
>> He's like, "You don't have to return
your library books on time
or ever."
>> [laughter]
>> But then
Jesus
will be like,
"Hey, maybe you shouldn't be joking
around about Hitler.
>> [applause]
>> It's actually a really sensitive subject
>> [laughter]
>> you shouldn't make light of."
But then Hitler will be like,
>> [laughter]
>> "We should start a podcast together."
>> Then Jesus is like,
"You shouldn't have put this in this
special. That's That's not good.
They don't like it very much."
He's telling me to stop doing this joke
right now.
>> [laughter]
>> But then Hitler is like,
"Keep going.
>> [laughter]
>> Keep going until they laugh."
"You can always edit it out." That's
what he's saying.
Oh, no.
That's what's going on in my head right
now.
>> [applause]
>> I grew up a very Christian, like
conservative Christian.
Um that's why I know a lot about Jesus
and Hitler.
Just part of my culture.
But I grew up a very sheltered I had a
very sheltered upbringing. Like there
were certain movies I wasn't allowed to
watch. Like I wasn't allowed to watch
All Dogs Go to Heaven.
>> [laughter]
>> Because a lot of Christians believe that
dogs don't go to heaven.
Yeah, which is a a weird thing to
believe. But I think they get it from a
verse in the Bible.
If you have your Bibles with you, open
to the book
>> [laughter]
>> Sorry, I just traumatized a lot of
people in here.
Sorry about that.
>> [laughter]
>> No. It's not in the Bible. They just
made that up. I don't know why they
made that up. It's a weird thing to
believe. Just let the dogs go to heaven.
Dogs are cool.
Right?
Dogs act way more Christian than a lot
of Christians that I know.
Right? They like love people
unconditionally.
Yeah.
>> [applause]
>> They help the blind.
They're always dry humping. Like they're
already Christian. Just like let them
into heaven.
Come on.
>> [cheering and applause]
[laughter]
>> When you're at church, I participated in
the children's Christmas pageant. And I
played the role of the Virgin Mary.
Thank you.
And I yeah, I took it very seriously. I
went full method.
>> [laughter]
>> I stayed in character as a virgin for
years and years and years.
Way after production wrapped. I was so
committed to the part.
Till today.
No, I am
I remember I didn't know what virgin
meant. So I asked one of the older kids.
I asked one of the wise men. I was like
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, what is virgin?
And he said, a virgin is someone who has
never had sex.
And I was like, okay, cool. Follow-up
question.
>> [laughter]
>> What What sex?
And he said sex is when adults wrestle.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, okay, cool. No more
follow-up questions.
Now I know what sex is. Thank you.
But not long after that, my mom sat me
down to give me the talk. And the first
thing she said to me was, "Hey, do you
know what sex is?"
And I just learned, so I was like,
"Yeah."
It's not just for adults though, kids
can do it, too.
>> [laughter]
>> We do it all the time in the backyard.
>> She's like, "What? Wait."
>> [laughter]
>> "Who's we? What are you talking about?"
So I named my brothers.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, "Sometimes I practice with
the dog, but he doesn't like it very
much. He tries to get away, and I really
have to hold him down."
Maybe that's why I wasn't allowed to
watch All Dogs Go to Heaven. Actually, I
never watched that.
Thinking about it.
She's just keeping me away from dog
stuff.
But we cleared the confusion, and I
found out that I was a virgin.
And I was like, "Oh, so I'm a virgin,
like the Virgin Mary?"
And she was like, "Yeah, you're exactly
like the Virgin Mary."
And the one thing I knew about Virgin
Mary was that she gave virgin birth
to Jesus.
And I learned from the church that Jesus
was going to come back someday.
Did you guys learn that?
You're learning it now?
So, with that knowledge in my head,
after that, every time I went to the
doctor, my doctor, she would always ask
me the same question. She would say,
"Is there a chance you could be
pregnant?"
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> And every time,
I was like,
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> "There's always a chance."
"We better check."
>> [laughter]
>> "I'm feeling pretty chosen today."
>> I got really good at peeing into a cup.
Cuz I did it every time. I would fill it
up all the way.
I thought that more pee that was in the
cup, the better chance I had of
>> [laughter]
>> giving birth to Jesus.
I was like, "Jesus will be in this
cup."
So, I'd fill it up. I would let my cup
runneth over with pee.
Hey, thank you guys so much. REALLY
APPRECIATE IT.
>> [music]
[applause]
[music]
>> COME ON.